https://www.cscc.org.sg/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Cornerstone Community Church > Privacy Policy
Personal Data Protection Act 2012 At Cornerstone Community Church (CSCC) we take seriously the responsibility and stewardship of Personal Data that is collected through our website and other church registration systems. CSCC works diligently to ensure that the church is in compliance with the standards and regulations set forth by the government of Singapore as outlined in the Personal Data Protection Act of 2012.Your Personal Data By interacting with, submitting information to or signing up for any organized activity offered by CSCC, you agree and consent to the collecting, using, disclosing and sharing of your Personal Data, for the purpose of engagement and operational planning of activities, as well as communication of events, programmes, and church-related information that pertains to CSCC.Accessing your Personal Data You may access your Personal Data held by CSCC by filling in the Request form available from the church office. Please allow for approximately 30 days for the processing of your Personal Data. The Data Protection Officer (DPO) of CSCC will release the requested data upon verification of your Identity Card and signed request form.Withdrawal of Consent You may withdrawal consent given with respect to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal data at any time by sending a formal written request to the DPO at privacy@cscc.org.sg.Confidentiality CSCC will ensure that all Personal Data is kept confidential and accessible to appointed authorized personnel for the purpose in which the information is being sought.Retention and Management of Data Your Personal Data will be retained by CSCC as necessary for the fulfilment of purposes stated so as to satisfy any legal, regulatory, programmatic or accounting requirements.CSCC will retain Personal Data Details relating to Membership, Baptism, Marriage and Death for an indefinite period for record purposes. Other records will be maintained up to 7 years before being anonymized if they are no longer needed.Data Protection Officer CSCC will appoint a Data Protection Officer (DPO) as warranted under the PDPA Openness Obligation portion of the Act. The DPO(s) will be responsible in helping to ensure compliance with the PDPA and its policies. The DPO will be the primary point person when special requests, questions or disputes are raised with regard to the data collection of an individual.Contacting Us We have taken great measures to ensure that your privacy is constantly respected in your interactions with CSCC concerning data collection. If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our privacy practices, please contact us by emailing the DPO at privacy@cscc.org.sg.
Full details
×
Contact Event Manager
Book your tickets
Update Personal Details
Your ticket for
Tickets count
1
